To. Me and it.
To. Him you need.
To move.
To.
The who.
Knew who to.
This is the story of Michael Blake former
paratrooper one of the many eggs G.I.'s
were found themselves drawn back to those
places they had known during the war
seeking the old drill of excitement but
never finding it. But Blake's whisperings
story different from those Maybe you've
heard of well the end of it anyway it hit
the headlines at the time but it will bring
up here at the village of St Hilda's
they are in the rugged mountains of the
South of France. The summer dawn comes
quiet day to the village perched here on
the. To the precipice. They will it's
preached always the first awake was
on his way to the church when Saddam.
The bells were ringing the bells that have
been silent ever since the disappearance
of a god with
a single day are the famous green glow
that made this village an object of the
religious to the sick the maimed
and the baseball for nearly
a thousand years to Father Duro it meant
that the gauntlet had come home for the
ballad been made of the bell we should never
really again until it returned but it
wasn't there in the nature which had been
empty so long why at the end of the bells
ringing and who was ringing them.
I'm
to them
he
eh
C.F.C.'s
I'm
Jim.
Jim
I'm
Jim.
Yes come home. Brought it from
nobody. There was nobody there.
Only. The dead man.
If he ring the bell to sing the going to
come home. He was dealt the grand nobody
would of. Change Liz Kelly.
An American. So there it was the miracle
of the Goddess for the come home with no
one to bring in the Bell the grime with
no man alive to pollute and of course the
mystery of the dead man. With the end
of the story. But this story has really
begun many years earlier.
This nineteen bloody war.
Your life liberation of
the South of France.
One survivor respect around
behind the German lines.
I'm close.
And. I set
my sketches. The ideas that correspondent
and over the papers battle scenes
impressions and explore Oh now.
I see yours is like Utena play
a game of human species getting at our
journey. Whatever it is I've changed
passport was and I've lost touch. I was
educated in England and I know to check my
father was a coach in those
days the pose a Russian is
a check for us to. Get out.
American the wasting of
a lot of ammunition. Only to Michel
you get the JAMMA nine hundred on the
counter-attack don't nobody interested
to see. OK to let you into the
jeans he was going. To let you go
the Gemini show. But I think this.
Open.
I told you I sketched. In
a little she got. The green
glove of
a very valuable. This is Blake you have
to go it's yours it was another make you
rich for the rest of your life. Because
those gems. I told you I sketched that many
a sideline in peacetime I'm
an art dealer antiques
a shop in London. Even York
probably had a bit. Of
a given he's. Never been
like I described with
a fortune of the one collective
would be demolished.
She would laugh when. We were looking for
you everything we show you dropped from
the plane. Don't worry the underground
has had many other good for you. Jim.
Jim's account a checking one
thousand times I gotta get
a message. Message me that one. Of cos
the other.
Champagne method. You might.
Just waiting to.
Make. It is that really feel good. As you.
Can See That is like from.
New York when it comes.
To coming right now no no not now or ever
Germans are dreaming that's why we drink
so they're American. Sometimes.
We think yes we drink to you our
first American in the world came with
thank the English to the French. And.
We had. The music. Of this favorite
to. It isat the gate to. Where
we played together here
it was before the war.
Which will be out of
the well. Maybe.
We found him and methadone but all supposed
to be best because to speak when we
found him he said Thompson imagine
the message would do says I.
Thought I was doing something for his
country. He died for nothing. That man swore
to Jim for
a tax. Treaty. Which kind of help. Are
you ready most. Countries.
Can't. She has not spoken
since the reason is quite God bless you
for getting your bag Michel. You found it
yes in the ruins was
a lot is hard it is better to just think
you know I keep it for you some day you
can come back for it after
the law is clear you keep.
That was the end of the beginning they
took to the words. And the story stopped
dead for several years.
It started again one fine August morning
in Paris the years have been tough for
Michael Blake everything had gone wrong
so Michael came back for somewhere in the
south of France he knew of
a glove which was worth
a fortune. But
someone had been waiting for Michael
Blake's return and. The platform on
which we're now standing is
a hundred eighty eight feet above the ground.
A total head of the structure is nine
hundred and seventy five feet now if you
continue with me cannot be passed over
there to be able to get
a good look at the same in all
the bridges allowing. This way.
Thank you look over your shoulder and some
of the little men to gracious to. You
come this way.
Because of elevators he
tries to stop the time in.
The street can you tell me the
time. Ten minutes to twelve time
a commission elevator. You can look down.
Now because you've seen the river saying
which close to Paris if you look you all
messed up on Monument the Austrian.
The trouble with you is
Jim. I gotta take like
a seriously or not take it all
in the night. Ready getting it.
And then you say. To me.
Well I want to chuck my old
buddy Chuck. Right Mike
you've heard me talk Mike I'll stay to
get Mike this is Chris Christie. In
a big favor didn't. Even want to.
Write. In finish.
I'm going to. Get
a job. In
a week. Why
is it an article. I will be asked
a lot of questions. And interact with it
all about this morning while with family
and in
a. Minute. Sharing tourist psychopathic
stranger in town I'm
a gimmick getting to have. An official
or unofficial message is any reason
why Madeleine was not. Attending. And
believe me. I like I haven't robbed
a bank and killed anybody I'm not
an international spy reason. X.X.
. He danced in this.
House got me into more
trouble.
He went home well I still knew
where. The first trial the Michael
a gas. Tank missed.
We grew old I'll get your guitar player
play for solitude. Perimeter. You
know I will make these rash promises
about. Never in front of witnesses who.
Didn't even have
a chance in we're. Kind of. Going
to think it's great. She
have an extra week maybe.
Because we're going to come to money come.
You can come six o'clock train in the
morning. Well I think it's
a real diffuse not actions like that made
me feel much me. How I Met Your friend
Jimmy I was invited to get what you mean
which was stay together which I didn't go
to college. And looks like we
spent the night together on the phone to.
Believe. Him I go break this part of me
aside and said you might come here about
will you please return with us to
your hotel. Why. I'm Inspector
phobia Barry's police department that is
our information regarding the man who lies
dead in your room. Eight.
You know this then. Sound from
then on the Eiffel Tower Why do you recall
having seen. The life of me I can't
remember. For the life of you perhaps you
had better and. I want is my mother's
knowledge of this matter. Have you
seen that person. Also in the
ivory tower. Remember that is
definitely whether you know
that to lie on behalf of
a criminal is to render yourself
an existing don't call me
a criminal why should she lie that
you're hearing the I didn't say she lie.
So neither of you can recall what
you know to me it just chance or
a tiger just drew the three of you together.
The doctor says it's been dead for
thirty six hours out there right away
during that time. A little cabaret down the
street I don't know if a place called
a sleeping carriage and. If I was here
it is well you spoke the truth there are
witnesses to prove it. What are you doing.
Spending my money you got any objection
that is the reason. I came
here I came here to kill
a guy left his body in my bedroom. And
arrest me I cannot arrest you. But you will
be transferred to another room one of
my men will be on hand we'll call it
a protective custody. Is the
three elements in your favor.
Strongest. Young ladies take substantiating
or second you stayed out tonight
instead of disposing of the deceit it
might have been possible. You seem to be
a reasonably intelligent person if you'd
kill this man I believe you would have
destroyed his drawing. It was
a day. I mean if you miss you when you fail
to identify him because it's obvious he
needed a means to identify you but it
also indicates that there is somewhere
a link or
a connection between your presence in
friends and his THAT. All of you is
a down. Lieutenant of United
States airborne infantry.
In
a suit. You want to die whenever and
I want my friend outside. My watch
that the policeman is wearing
a cavity there is no policeman's or. A
right he's got that's all
this is yet thanks to.
The priest back in place. Back
to full they're going to play.
Secretary. Back to where. I wait
a minute you think I'm going
to hang around here provide
a link when to come back.
Next week next week and.
Yeah. Yeah I will take time out.
You know. I think the problem. With.
The in.
Shame. No smoke I speak of the English much
much you don't know that when you bump
into me this morning who had you to phone
me. Alone which is illegal I was guilty
of the same brush. You took to
make it a goal to stand here in
a million fantasy that when you go to
send in NG I go to County Calif right I'm
going on NG intelligible to I
know I'm a little my wife she has
a Nobel in English name the I'm still
stranded and then being an American you
wouldn't know. But if you would wish to
sell you'll still the money my wife and I
did and I stripped.
That. Seat for
complimenting. The boss I regret your project
on traveling light of course I forgot
that I liked.
It is
a political matter. And
.
That's what I'm asking you. I was
reading and I quite Thank you I.
Don't want to.
Get into. Without.
Evident in
a night. Train right now. Seven
hundred francs and ninety nine.
Thank you very much. It can make it. Such
a little dangerous shipping. What really
happened to the policeman it was that he
went out on
a date or something I don't know the
particulars All right so I kill him till.
He's unchanged. Which is keeping
you awake. If you're to get to.
The place walk out on but you can't run
away like will catch up with me anyhow
within two days two days
until the other friend and
a fan what is this and I'll listen I'll
tell you what it is is none of your
business and I don't want any more
your help can not offering my help as
a customer and I'm going
to do it deep if you're
a kid that way I'll be in jail. Get this
I'm going to stick by you until I know
what this is all about in self-defense
I'll do it believe me I'll be with you day
and night. Complaining. Michael
tell me I'm not the kind of
beast you. This is
a man.
With
a pipeline up. From the South as if he was
supposed to get out of Mexico are nasty
to kill at. What age tell me but I didn't
kill any man face now what is all this
later on the train. Yes. I want to
talk about the way the manager.
Agapanthus you have to come
out of the other way. If you
doesn't tell me and I meet
with one of the stations.
Had to take them up.
Then he went to sleep.
Now but we will.
Be breakfast. Where do we go from here.
To. Try to find. One.
On the field is shaped like
a bird. Flying at the bailout. Was
a war. We want to go back and find.
But some. Parents.
Count too much. Of
a night. The
American attack last
night. It arrives here in.
My dear.
God. To get into one of the. Attacks.
That's.
About. Thousand years in
heaven. I don't understand.
That's the village up there
only going to. Come over here.
This is a very famous spot
a local legend is called
a sharp point at the shop you can see. This
is Latin L B I want to battle over the
moon I thought you said
do you think you are
a funny one but this is way in the past is
in the mood what's happening way up that
road. Is the only one connected the
edge of the outside world but an L.D.R.
Attack that was in the rear he led his
men down to this spot but the only other
route and were to possible go practice
Well that was the end of the Morse you can
see the go track over there it starts from
the village going to the precipice and
it's
a very dangerous cost on the face of the
cliff it will see the track clearly as it
reaches the valley and big
bags across rough country to
a point directly below it and
a kind again very steeply up up up
to this point. What the village
Anyway it's not what is there now it's
what was there one way in the pan well.
In the past.
This is an empty.
Profit yesterday so and it's got
the same one I said about to get
a different system.
And ideas helped you along prod
money trying to read it is
a God No because it was not always people
who used to come here and thousands in
the Gamma gone about to go eat it and.
Who could imagine that it would not be
safe there but you can imagine what
a dancer brought pictures prices up to
change and think the world deleted enough I
don't know your collector a
twelve million francs for
a stone to divide the gauntlet I think
like what they are but the one hundred
thousand pounds is the easy part and I did
a travelling oppressively I believe that
one day. Become whole and then you will
ring the bell or you know about the battle
to the bell that has never run since the
day the gauntlet was stolen will never be
again until it comes back yes I read that
somewhere but. I give out
a. Good
bye darling.
Run Dubnyk to get the money column I.P.O.
In the morning guys but even if you can
combine business with. Reality here is the
next degree show me that the casino.
Is telegram right for you from T.V.
I decoded it.
This is approaching this road we've given
up. On him and then there's. My wife to
pay as my son is not trying to.
Not.
Let me.
The only thing that.
I don't you see Chris another
big bad luck this proves it.
You're not to blame because the price
is destroyed by the war. All right my
comeback if you weren't ready to say things
I was. Nothing like disgrace. You know
when I walked out of that door years ago
things they went from bad to worse. I
thought that when I came back and found
a glove that might help.
My make up on. But if they
optioned don't go. I'd like to have
a check. I
get it from every. Rather good. With
metaphor. Polish title.
Just to clarify matters I've been keeping
a tab on USE THE WALL TO MY York office I
must say that it is at the time. That man
killed Michael. Yes I did read about that
in the papers current event the man who
was beaten to death. I imagine anyone who
comes in decided to double cross somebody
. To make
a deal behind somebody back so you killed
my dear young lady I never killed anyone
in my life that even during the war the
Germans of the Palm Isabella grabber to the
French were gonna be one of their spies so
convenient arrangement beside the point
you're broke that's why you're going to
France to cash in on the glove so it's
still here. It might be
why the tell me play.
Emmy. Don't touch it. Not yet.
Today Blake. But it isn't the first time
blood been shed for the god of candles
in. A green glove the same thing you want
to talk about my help your hair I warrant
a vision of your arrest and it can.
Really believe I killed that game I'm
a detective on the train he was
shot dead you left your coat
a piece is too pretty for the part of the
police to. Themselves for they think you
get a break what you they're after the
frame just of opportunity not if like
a lot of nice effective
for that's where you put
a lot of color on how I don't want any I'll
get you one brand of your five thousand
dollars for the glove come here is
Pepe when I'm boxing said was the crab
a rough customer. Get out of my way.
To. Making.
A name is.
To. Aim.
To.
Remain whom it is. A good idea. To
be able to get. It to make up to break.
Even if you know what it Johnny and
I do try to get you to visit my great.
Game in which.
Man named.
He's.
The man who had. Traditionally from
a man. Bring him to the village and.
No more than fifty people.
He's
a good enough case when
you. Don't. Know. My
son.
He should be back immediately. Time is.
Now most to live. Here.
She tells me which happens. When we click
on the moment consumer choice about to.
Be shocked to see the beautiful new she.
Didn't repeat.
Everything but I'm but.
Maybe not with you.
And Madam nobody else. But it's
late for you to be out of your bed.
Tonight but I'm. Not.
Turning them down.
I didn't mean anybody. The police are
leaving. We might as well be going to shows
away. Something talking to the bank.
I promised that would keep
it thanks given to me.
Sounds nothing. Like to.
Do. I think she has
a right to see it I think you are too
there's nothing in it but I. Try.
Green gloves. So they'll
get to mountain village by
Monte Carlo very small which famous of
course for the gauntlets which was said to
be a Lisick and. That gauntlet
a center. Is it. Is it possible.
To. Send in.
Two thousand people. When
I went to Cuba to come.
To Paris and. Would come. To expect.
Him. To live he'll announce one died.
But no one knew.
Me.
Nobody around still think we should take
in the road and run into the place that we
figured something out we've got a
leg a stand right now I haven't got
a leg don't walk on tired and. I can't
imagine how you try and send those clouds
over there in the rain any minute let's go.
Live to my thank Paris and make sure to
catch up with us Sunday ideally along those
can happen in America. Which you know I
must believe in there. Which attempts to
close the strange and she just fainted and
she hit her head this will prove to dish
that except turning to thinking and. Do
you know before the glove man it shouldn't
come back because it would pay off. No
man. Enough to go I was you
know Zizi. Even wanted to
marry. But I wouldn't. Look away or.
Has no idea she's.
The same in.
The in.
The middle with
a. Yes
. He
just met the pope back this
is John by the process. Was.
Well we'll take a jog Yes mama move
a tall guy comes in the car or we have
no car. What we're hanging San Rafael we
thought it was you get a bus from
here this is no bus to me but we have
a rule and we can try your
clothes while you sleep. It's
a warm day you. Committed.
You can now read.
This where Mr or Mrs Smith Mr or Mrs John
Smith because because the police because
of them the reason you do this is.
Yes Well if you like to sign for as
dining. Mr and Mrs Smith
just write the image
with. A rolled from
a gown as myrow from the ship. If you we
both come to Rome and take off all of your
toes. My wife is
a little bit shy Yes You see we just got
married to day to day all across the
country all I. Know the call to.
Give the brandy Yes mamma said you won't
catch code you can take to the kitchen
come.
See you later mom.
You know we are. Miss you and that
I was going to honeymoon walking.
To reduce the. Property being
used to such things exist.
We'll both be so comfortable
and with just enough of us on with our
best why I want to conquer the God I want
wanting store of it. And
my husband went down down.
On. You need another to
one with me and I'm.
Glad you think you just.
Keep it thank you.
Think.
Would you like another brandy I'm sure. Is
good to lining the stomach for my son to
say what an idiot and it'll keep your
spirits up the minute you let the train all
on your wedding night know they are by the
way my wife said the Dr is down to that
. Effect and. If it has been the night.
Before for a cozy bed was did you drop
into sense not seeing I came back
a night for that girl looks
like an event but it improves.
You to. Bandy and they give
Brandy Alfonse why I should have
mine. Is nothing like brandy
to. Lift up the ears.
Thank you. For the something I want to
tell you but I'm better off to be use
a nice. View of you with an amiable eyes
she still faces but Friend me and have
we our best was
a major when I tell you
of all she's on. That
.
Smack. In that.
Area is it. Came here to.
There.
My.
Mind if I kiss you. Don't
say that to us twice.
Thank you for you. Right.
Now I try and talk to. You
wanted to help me. On my
way you can't do this to murder you haven't
done it to prove it finished Well I'm
not so sure they can't that's
why we've got to think of
a way out before we get in any deeper.
Sleep. When you go
downstairs to do that.
Last night I can't get out.
The first time in my life.
You know I have
a bit bucket of money. To stay
here I'm going to handle myself. I
don't stray we're going to. Everything
just the way of getting the game.
Played out to be then I come. Into.
The.
Know there's nothing.
That we. Are going to come to
we have
a guidebook. To measure the cost. And
you get yourself an interest.
In this and I think they have.
To finish. The season over get in
a still image. Point
out. You going
to to graduate. It's
a little town about the animal. Run
company I want you to do something for me
Christmas gotta be fast I'm taking
the glove back as an L.T.R.
Now. Mike how can I miss
a check everything is going to be at the
Cabaret the casino to tonight I want you
to go there Chris corrected tension keep
him interested talk to him until three
o'clock by three the most important part
of three o'clock and listen very carefully
Chris it's three o'clock tell him where I'm
going. To come ask you right away and I
shall idea and you can expect
a fall back on that is man of the village
at five o'clock on those roads analogize
it and we'll have the county's boys right
the middle of eleven and let me tell nice
they must be got it. I think since.
Cabaret the casino telekinetic
free crack at the Fleet up there at five.
But might we should we should really took
his out there in time.
Actually. Doing nice.
And enjoys
a funny name. Joining
me for the. Time. But
I. Kept on
coming up. The money but
certainly you wish to send
a message. Returning to. Albany is
leaving just behind you know as
a sovereign nation of the top teams
in the way that it now sounds.
Like you've been there and figure
it. Out on you both later right.
By Brandi Felix. You know given. That is
because we did a little. You know you got
a lovely biscuit he keeps. Such
a good chance. You'll just
end up broke the object of
a man. In his mind taking
it back you get it.
But it is
a better way than the tables of how he got
your getting ready when he clinched it
McNabb. Believe it or not no. IP
it said age or give up too easily.
I say to heart. That's why maybe the
Patterson that. Discretion sometimes the
better part of valor but. What about Mike
when you know he wanted to be he didn't
do
a relay but who's to blame he didn't have
to go to Paris. That I feel is is that
he actually helped you could you get him
out of this but I. Will as well it's
nothing I can think of. The very
charming come out of my name's
Tom. Is that all you seem to be what else
is it isn't it don't you want to know
where he ends up is it about how much
you're aware that it was that without
a stereotype happy maybe the brandy
Pelosi thank you might say the positive.
Things in this because I want to even
talk to him why not if you. See me at the
station the next and then when he can't
you have to get him. Use out of he wanted
to go to it you know why discuss it I would
say the cash generated really I must
have
a pledge. To take the class to. Take
in the glove package and. Wanted
to get at. It you know I couldn't care
less what my training in the country
situation but to get him out
of God that can. Could buy.
Me down you're not
a lawyer it's probably going to drink
enough to change his mind to the right side
of. The trunk and then in ten
minutes but but come on already to.
Become
a good thing to say stop me and of course
going to meet the demand it's going to
restaurants Madam.
Even the Mrs John Smith recipient of nice
under six isn't really missing I'm going
to be in the new show.
Good.
Good. And then Blake will be ahead
of the car would run him about
a block you three will walk to the
village and I'll wait here for the come.
To get
good. To get.
A. Big. Big
big.
Big.
To the village.
To something beyond
just check. Man tribal.
Village. To go track tell him
to watch for him from the.
I'm going. To close the trap.
The is is in the.
Live in the.
In the
in the.
The in the. In the.
In.
I want to make
a deal. I only want to glom. In
.
In. The in the in.
The in.
He was afraid it was
a jump. In
.
The jump and I'm thinking my friend the
bomb not the killed two in my opinion
a plan. In.
The in.
When. The
people like.
To. Live.
In.
In any man in.
The if you think.
This is
a it isn't news. To me it is
a whim it
has. A new
enemy.
This is.
Our climate mechanics. And if you're in
a bad deal. Of the day the
globe first thing is.
Going to. BE What is different matter.
Right now something you can. Every
day accept. My signature like.
My neighbor got me
a moment. Of who is going to come. Out
numbered surely. Thank you Keith
when
the fifty eight eight.
Eight. Eight
who
I am when
a who. I
am who I
am who I am who I am
who I am
who
I am who I
am who I am I
am who I
am
who I am
who I
am
who. I am.
C.N.N.
. NEWSROOM
. Nobody there was little
is there. No one except.
The Daily Mail.
From. The police on him
train from the Pentagon.
You're all right. It's been another matter
of the town. In that me too but you
didn't do it my dream. Run of men in the
village one of them is already complex.
Gloves come. Up in the village they're
saying to me today that the miracle of the
Goddess come not the means by
which case. Good luck to you.